carboniteaddon.com 2008-12-19

# Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY

We, Carbon Based Creations, LLC or “Company”, respect the privacy of our online visitors and of users of our online Services (such as the online forum). We collect information on or through this Website that can personally identify You only when it is voluntarily offered by You. For example, we collect personally identifiable information to respond to questions and comments about us and our products and Services.

PERSONAL INFORMATION. Any personal information that You provide to our Web site will stay safe, private, and secure. We will use this information to improve how we operate and offer our software, to communicate with You about our software, and to provide effective customer support when necessary. We will not resell Your information to outside sources. We will not share Your information with any third parties with the exception of verified secure ecommerce transaction providers.   
We do not share any of the personal information You provide to us with any third party other than service providers of ours who assist us in providing the information and/or Services we are providing to You. To the extent that we do share Your personal information with a service provider, we would only do so if that party has agreed to comply with our privacy standards as described in this Privacy Policy. 

NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION. Any non-personal information, communications, content and material You send to this Website or to us by e-mail are on a non confidential basis. We are free to use and reproduce any such information freely, and for any purpose whatsoever. Specifically, we will be free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques contained in such information for any purpose, including developing, manufacturing or marketing products. Any information You send to this site must be truthful, must not violate the rights of others, and must be legal. 

INFORMATION THAT WE MAY COLLECT FROM OUR USERS. We may collect the following information when You sign up for a Service or when You purchase software:  
First name, last name, e-mail, Your address, phone number   
For processing transactions, we also collect either credit card information or bank information, and billing information, depending on Your form of payment. We do not store any credit card information after Your transaction is complete.   
Information concerning software downloaded  
Your computer configuration (such as Your operating system, connection speed, and peripherals)  
IP Address. When a user visits this Website, we may collect the IP address that requested the display. This address is collected for the purpose of exercising our ability to restrict access to the Website by users who have violated our Terms of Service.   
Cookies. Like many other companies, we use "cookie" technology, where our servers deposit special codes on a visitor's computer. The sole purpose of cookies is to enhance Your online experience. Cookies are small data files that are stored on Your computer by websites. Through Your Web browser, cookies are only used by the Website that wrote the cookie. This information helps us determine in the aggregate the total number of visitors to the site on an ongoing basis and the types of Internet browsers (e.g., Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) and operating systems (e.g., Windows or MacIntosh) used by our visitors. Data stored in a cookie from Company is only accessible by Company. Personal information stored in our cookies is limited to Your Username. This information enables us to operate our Service, allows customized advertising, lets You automatically sign in when You visit, and offers other operational Website activities to enhance Your on-line visits. The information in our cookies is kept private and secure. 

USE OF COLLECTED INFORMATION. Your Username, e-mail address, and password will be used to uniquely identify You as a user on the Website. We may use or display Your username for the purposes of chat identification and/or forum postings. Other identifying information collected during the sign up process or through other voluntary means may be used to calculate aggregate demographics figures and/or facilitate our ability to direct advertisements to Your Web browser. Your Web browser or software that You use to access the Website may transmit certain geographic information and information regarding the capabilities or features of Your computer and/or software to us. We may use this information to calculate aggregate statistics about our user community or for security purposes, and may provide information such information to advertisers and/or partners in aggregate form only. We may use Your information to deliver to You and to bill You for software purchased on the Website, and to communicate with You concerning Your account and customer service issues. This may include verifying authorization of credit card usage before any purchase of software. 

E-MAIL/OPT-OUT. When You sign up as a Website user, or download any software from Company, You may be asked to allow us to communicate with You via e-mail about special offers. [If the former statement is not true, please delete.] You have the option to uncheck or check a box during the sign up process that will prevent this. Any e-mail we send to You will contain information about opting-out of any further mailings. 

THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISING. It is important that You understand that advertisers or websites that link to the Website may collect personal information about You. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of, other advertisers or websites. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on the Website. These companies may use information about Your visits to this Website in order to help them provide relevant ads to users (this information does not include name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number). 

SHARING INFORMATION. We may disclose Your information if there is a violation of the Terms of Service or if we have a good faith belief that the law requires it. 

CHAT & MESSAGING. Company may choose to operate message boards and/or chat areas where users can exchange ideas and communicate with one another. When posting to a message board or chat area, it is important for You to understand that the information is being made publicly available in an online environment. Any information and content posted is the sole responsibility of the individual user. 

NON-US CUSTOMER INFORMATION. If You are a user who is accessing the Website from outside the United States, the personal information You submit to Company will be sent to and stored by Company. The personal information practices in this Privacy Policy apply to all users worldwide. 

AGREEMENT WITH COMPANY POLICIES. We may modify this policy at any time, in our sole discretion and all modifications will be effective immediately upon our posting of the modifications on this Website. By using the Website, or by purchasing software, You signify Your understanding and agreement to the Privacy Policy stated here, and to the Terms of Service. If You do not agree with our policies, please do not use the Website or Services.   
For additional information about our on-line privacy practices, contact 

privacy@carboniteaddon.com.

Are You concerned about our use of personal information?

If, for any reason, You are concerned with the way that we may be using Your personal information, You may request that we cease to use Your information or You may contact Company at 

privacy@carboniteaddon.com.
